http://www.numberplates.com/company/privacy

Sign in
Lines are closed.
4.9/5
(Based on 1022010,220 reviews)
Finance options available
Home
Company
Privacy policy (You are here)
Privacy policy
When you use our services, you are trusting us with your information.
This is a big responsibility and we work hard to protect your information and put you in control. Together with our Terms & Conditions and our Terms of Use they govern our relationship with you in relation to this website.
1. Data Protection & Privacy
Regtransfers is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully, in accordance with the ePrivacy Regulation (ePR) and General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
We may collect limited information about you to enable us to process any orders you may place and to provide services you may request. We may also, with your consent, send you news, updates and offers. Our intention is to provide you with the best possible service. All personal data is held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.
We aim to process information about you in a fair and transparent manner and to ensure that information we hold is accurate and up to date. The aim of this document is to provide you with sufficient information for you to be able to understand what we are doing with your data.
You have the right to object to the collection and/or processing of personal data. If you have objections or concerns, are unsure how we are handling or using information about you, or you think we could improve our privacy information please contact our Data Controller.
Data controller
Ian Clayton, Regtransfers.co.uk, 139 High Street South, Dunstable, Bedfordshire, LU6 3SS. Email: gdpr@regtransfers.co.uk.
This is also the address to send emails informing us of errors or inaccuracies in data. If we are made aware of any errors or inaccuracies we will delete or correct the relevant data promptly.
We will not share your data with any third party except where required to do so in response to lawful request by government or law enforcement agencies, or with your consent.
2. Data Processing
Regtransfers collects and processes data for the purposes set out below. Each use of data is conducted according to a lawful basis and the basis for each category of data use is specified, along with the data types concerned.
2.1 Order/purchase processing
Lawful basis
Data types
Legitimate Interests. Our 'legitimate interest' for collecting and processing some of your personal data is fulfillment of your order: an essential part of our business.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
Bank account details
2.2 Valuation services
Lawful basis
Data types
Legitimate Interests. Our 'legitimate interest' for collecting and processing some of your personal data is fulfillment of your service request: an essential part of our business and necessary to provide you with the information you require.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
2.3 Sales & Purchase enquiries
Lawful basis
Data types
Legitimate Interests. Our 'legitimate interest' for collecting and processing this data is the need to respond fully to your product or service enquiry: an essential part of our business and necessary to provide you with the information you require.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
2.4 Magazine request
Lawful basis
Data types
Consent. With your express consent, we use your data in order to provide you with the products and services to which you have subscribed. We may contact you by post, email and/or phone/SMS.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
2.5 Subscription services
Lawful basis
Data types
Consent. With your express consent, we use your data in order to provide you with the products and services to which you have subscribed. We may contact you by post, email and/or phone/SMS.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
2.6 Marketing services
Lawful basis
Data types
Consent. With your express consent, we use your data in order to provide you with information regarding special offers, price reductions, registrations of specific relevance and similar information. We may provide this information to you by post, email and/or phone/SMS.
Full name
Postal address
Telephone number(s)
Email address(es)
Vehicle registration number
3. Cookies
A cookie is a simple text file that is stored on the visitor's computer, enabling us to recognise regular visitors and to customise our service accordingly. No personal information about the user is stored in, or retrieved from, the cookie files.
Regtransfers uses cookies to enable us to provide an enhanced, personalised service to our visitors (for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your data without having to re-enter your username and password). Our cookies do not enable us to see any other information from the visitor's computer, and they pose no threat to your security or privacy.
The cookies we sometimes use are listed below, along with brief explanations of their purposes.
Cookie name
Purpose
utma, utmt, utmb, umtc, utmv and utmz (aka Google Analytics)
Recognises you when you return to our site and track the pages you visit, estimate our audience size, monitor traffic levels and search queries.
FullName
Stores the full name of the currently logged-in user on the Regtransfers auction site. Expires with the end of the current session. Improves site performance and speed.
Httpreferrer
If present, specifies the site the user came from to reach our site. Used for general, anonymous statistical analysis.
domain, referer, source, SourceName, SourceData
All five of these do basically the same thing; they determine which link, if any, the user followed to reach our site (e.g. one in our newsletter, or a promotional email etc). This allows us to display the correct phone number for enquiries. It also allows us to assess how effective our various communication methods are at generating traffic.
Affcode
Identifies which affiliate partner link the user followed to reach our website (where applicable). Used to credit sales commission to affiliate partners.
RegisteredUsersId, RegGUID
Internal user IDs relating to the currently logged in user on the Regtransfers Auction site. These cookies are required if you wish to use our auction service.
RememberMe, EmailAddress
If the customer so desires, s/he can have us save their email address for future logins to the Regtransfers Auction site to save them having to type it again. A customer convenience feature.
WLUserID
Used by our Regalert service to remember the customer's Regalert login and thus save them having to type it on future visits. A customer convenience feature.
MyRTContactID, MyRTGUID
Internal user IDs relating to the currently logged in user in Regtransfers. These cookies are required if you wish to use our online order-tracking service.
AffiliateLogin
Internal user ID relating to the currently logged in user in the affiliate system. This allows registered affiliate partners to access the affiliate system features.
RTSessionID
A unique number used to track a user (anonymously) throughout the site. Used for debugging if a customer encounters an error. Enables us to see the path the user followed through the site and, hopefully to replicate and fix the error.
Searches
Stores a list of searches the visitor does on our site. If the visitor requests a magazine or signs up to our Regalert service, this cookie can be used to offer a relevant list of number plates by email or SMS.
dtEnter
The date and time the user arrived at the site during the current 'session'. Used rarely to analyse trends in traffic using the website.
user_transaction_ids
Stores purchase data (plate, price etc) which is sent to Google Analytics. This does not contain sensitive personal data.
Please be aware that disabling cookies may make some services on some websites unavailable. Some cookies, such as those described as 'internal user IDs', are essential to the functionality of certain areas of the website. Login is not possible without them.
Web browsers such as Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome and Apple Safari have settings which allow the user to specify whether or not cookies are accepted. If you wish to alter your browser settings to prevent cookies being stored on your computer, please consult the help section of your web browser.
Your browser can be set to not accept cookies, but this would restrict your use of the Sites. If you want to find out more information about cookies, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org or to find out about removing them from your browser, go to http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.
Document last updated: 25/04/2018
Contents
Data protection
Data processing
Cookies
© 1982 - 2020 Registration Transfers Limited. All rights reserved. Registered in England. Company registration number 03933658. 'Regtransfers', 'Reg transfers' and the Regtransfers logo are registered trade marks of Registration Transfers Limited.
Credit subject to status and affordability. Terms & Conditions apply (details). Registration Transfers Limited, trading as Regtransfers, is a credit broker authorised and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority.
Transfer House, 139 High Street South, Dunstable, Bedfordshire, LU6 3SS. Tel: 01582 967777 | Email us.
We use cookies to collect some data when you use this website so it works better and is secure. Is that OK?
Privacy Policy Yes, OK
